So here's some things that happened this week that you should know about.
Governor Rhonda Satan wants to make it a felony if you have an undocumented immigrant in your home or car.
He also introduced HB 999, and that is a bill that, if passed, will remove all black sororities and fraternities from college campuses in Florida,
along with Latinx sororities and fraternities, along with gender studies, feminist studies and Jewish studies and more.
Speaking of education, Texas officials announced a state takeover of Houston's nearly 200,000 student public school district.
Yeah, fascist long game, getting control of the schools.
South Carolina Republicans proposed a bill that could subject women who have abortions to the death penalty.
And Tucker Carlson and The Wall Street Journal tried to blame the Silicon Valley bank crash on diversity.
Their thesis that they were too focused on hiring diverse people to see the money wasn't adding up.
The math wasn't math.
The math was saying, the threatened place and World Warkten things, right?
The versteck of The Wall Street Journal went through.
It was a real part of how бог had never published lands in your home or were saved by everyone,
but it was long for one of our Effect That Pass up.
Everything is an moeten dance lesson at once.
Oh yeah, guys, gonna do it again.
It's first time to make a patty kinky.
Now that we'll tell us, how did we get the super figured out?
Because we've got people found lados.
heavenly streamers to help those r accidental surfing in different viewsppamping of the thanh ї Rom.
Come andар time to know how complex stories,
So, this is just wild, but they don't empathize Were 갑 than these days.
Well, we've got them to be a question.
And theнибудь re-based In order thanhimi's all those films to happen.